Guide to the United Student Christian Council Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Conferences and Consultations, Series IV
  - USCC Conferences
    - Study conferences
      - Conference on Christian Faith and Law, University of Chicago, Chicago, IL, September 7-10, 1958
        - News Releases (Box 79, Folder 974)
        - Papers including "Christ and Law" by Wilber G. Katz (Box 79, Folder 975)
        - Program material (Box 79, Folder 976)
        - Prospectus (Box 79, Folder 977)
        - Report of National Conference on Christianity and Law (Box 79, Folder 978)
      - Bible Study Leaders Training Seminar, Kalamazoo College, Kalamazoo, MI, July 3-12, 1959
        - Address list (Box 79, Folder 979)
        - Bibliography (Box 79, Folder 980)
        - Evaluations (Box 79, Folder 981)
        - Memos (Box 79, Folder 982)
        - Report on the Bible Study Leadership Training Seminar (Box 79, Folder 983)
  - USCC Consultations
    - National Student Christian Consultation, Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 79, Folder 982)
    - National Student Christian Consultation, Minutes of the Planning Committee and notes taken by John Deschner and George Acebeda, 1944 (Box 79, Folder 983)
    - National Student Christian Consultation, Program material, 1944 (Box 79, Folder 984)
    - National Student Christian Consultation, Reports, 1944 (Box 79, Folder 985)
    - "Little Denison" Consultation minutes and reports, 1945 (Box 79, Folder 986)
    - WSCF Consultation, Correspondence re. Attendance, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 987)
    - WSCF Consultation, Correspondence with Roland Elliot, Robert Mackie, and Helen Morton, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 988)
    - WSCF Consultation, Expenses, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 989)
    - WSCF Consultation, General and miscellaneous, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 990)
    - WSCF Consultation, Program, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 991)
    - WSCF Consultation, Registrations, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 992)
    - WSCF Consultation, Report, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 993)
    - Regional Consultation Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 80, Folder 994)
    - Cincinnati Consultation, Statement concerning youth work--student work relations, January 8-9, 1947 (Box 80, Folder 995)
    - Nature of the Church Consultation, March 9, 1947 (Box 80, Folder 996)
    - USCC-SVM Consultation on the Future of the Student Volunteer Movement, October 3, 1947 (Box 80, Folder 997)
    - USCC Fall Consultation, Correspondence, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 998)
    - USCC Fall Consultation, Preparatory material, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 999)
    - USCC and United Christian Youth Movement Consultation, Summary report on "The Effective Evangelization of Industrial Youth", April 21-22, 1950 (Box 80, Folder 1000)
    - Consultation of Program Secretaries, Minutes, June 2, 1950 and March 29, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 1001)
    - Consultation on Work with International Students, Correspondence, March-May, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 1002)
    - USCC Consultation on Directions, Correspondence, December 1954-April 1955 (Box 81, Folder 1003)
    - USCC Consultation on Directions, Agenda, minutes and notes, May 3-5, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 1004)
    - Consultation on International Students, Correspondence, April-June, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 1005)
    - Consultation for Law Students and Professors, Rough notes summary (Box 81, Folder 1006)
  - World Student Christian Federation Conferences
    - WSCF General Committee
      - General Committee, La Roche Dieu, Bièvres, France, August 8-18, 1938
        - Minutes of the Meeting of the General Committee of the World's Student Christian Federation (Box 81, Folder 1007)
      - General Committee, Château de Bossey, Céligny, Switzerland, August 9-20, 1946
        - Correspondence, Delegates A-F (Box 81, Folder 1008)
        - Correspondence, Delegates G-L (Box 81, Folder 1009)
        - Correspondence, Delegates L-Z (Box 82, Folder 1010)
        - Correspondence, re. Delegate travel (Box 82, Folder 1011)
        - Minutes (Box 82, Folder 1012)
        - Preparatory material (Box 82, Folder 1013)
        - Preparatory material (Box 82, Folder 1014)
        - Proposal to send USCC delegates to WSCF General Committee (Box 82, Folder 1015)
        - Reports (Box 82, Folder 1016)
      - General Committee, Ontario Ladies' College, Whitby, Canada, August 9-22, 1949
        - Correspondence, re. Delegate travel (Box 82, Folder 1017)
        - Correspondence, re. International delegates (Box 83, Folder 1018)
        - Correspondence, re. Publicity (Box 83, Folder 1018a)
        - Finances (Box 83, Folder 1019)
        - General Committee documents (Box 83, Folder 1020)
        - General Committee documents (Box 83, Folder 1021)
        - Minutes (Box 83, Folder 1022)
        - Preparatory material (Box 83, Folder 1023)
        - Reports (Box 83, Folder 1024)
        - WSCF handbook (Box 83, Folder 1025)
      - General Committee, Nasrapur, India, 1953
        - Circular letters from WSCF (Box 83, Folder 1026)
        - Correspondence, Delegates to General Committee (Box 83, Folder 1027)
        - Memos from USCC (Box 83, Folder 1028)
        - Report on the conference and a summary of the closing address by Robert C. Mackie (Box 83, Folder 1029)
      - General Committee, Evangelical Academy, Tutzing, Germany, August 12-22, 1956
        - Correspondence, re. Delegates to General Committee (Box 83, Folder 1030)
        - General Committee documents (Box 83, Folder 1031)
        - General Committee documents (Box 84, Folder 1032)
        - Minutes (Box 84, Folder 1033)
        - Workbook (Box 84, Folder 1034)
    - WSCF Conferences in the United States of America
      - WSCF Conference, Park College, Parkville, MO, January 2-3, 1948
        - Briefing material (Box 84, Folder 1035)
        - Correspondence, re. Arrangements (Box 84, Folder 1036)
        - Correspondence, Delegates (Box 84, Folder 1037)
        - Correspondence, re. Leadership at conference (Box 84, Folder 1038)
        - Directory (Box 84, Folder 1039)
      - WSCF Bible Study Conference, Bowling Green, OH, August 25-30, 1949
        - Briefing material (Box 84, Folder 1040)
        - Conference documents (Box 84, Folder 1041)
        - Correspondence, re. Delegates to conference (Box 84, Folder 1042)
        - Correspondence, re. Program planning (Box 84, Folder 1043)
        - Finances for conference (Box 84, Folder 1044)
        - News Releases including Bowling Green Dateline (daily news release at the conference) (Box 84, Folder 1045)
        - Promotional material (Box 84, Folder 1046)
      - WSCF Bible Study Conference, Kalamazoo College, Kalamazoo, MI, June 18-27, 1951
        - Briefing material (Box 85, Folder 1047)
        - Correspondence, re. Arrangements for conference (Box 85, Folder 1048)
        - Correspondence, re. Conference planning (Box 85, Folder 1049)
        - Correspondence, re. Delegate quotas (Box 85, Folder 1050)
        - Correspondence, de Haller, Marie-Jeanne (Box 85, Folder 1051)
        - Correspondence, re. Scholarship fund (Box 85, Folder 1052)
        - Finances (Box 85, Folder 1053)
        - News clippings and news releases (Box 85, Folder 1054)
        - Program planning (Box 85, Folder 1055)
        - Registration cards (Box 85, Folder 1056)
    - Other WSCF Conferences
      - WSCF Summer Conference, Gwatt, Switzerland, Circular Letters and Correspondence, 1946 (Box 85, Folder 1057)
      - WSCF Summer Conference, Lundsberg, Sweden, Conference Materials including Prayers and summary of The Christian Student in the S.C.M. by R.H. Edwin Espy, August 1947 (Box 85, Folder 1058)
      - WSCF Summer Conference, Lundsberg, Sweden, Correspondence re. Delegates, April-August 1947 (Box 85, Folder 1059)
      - Second World Conference of Christian Youth, Oslo, Norway, Circular letters, correspondence, and memos, March- September 1947 (Box 85, Folder 1060)
      - Second World Conference of Christian Youth, Oslo, Norway, Delegate information and report of the World Youth Conference October 31-November 9, 1945 by the United States delegation (Box 86, Folder 1061)
      - Second World Conference of Christian Youth, Oslo, Norway, Pamphlets including Conference Handbook, Jesus Christ is Lord: a Service of Worship Prepared and Led by Delegates from the U.S.A., Jesus Kristus er Herre: Norwegian Lutheran Service of Holy Communion, and Jesus Christ is Lord: Notes on Worship at the Conference, and World Conference of Christian Youth: List of Delegates, July 1947 (Box 86, Folder 1062)
      - Second World Conference of Christian Youth, Oslo, Norway, Summaries of addresses and services includes notes by John Deschner, July 1947 (Box 86, Folder 1063)
      - Correspondence re. WSCF Summer Conferences, April-June 1948 (Box 86, Folder 1064)
      - Correspondence, Delegates to WSCF Summer Conferences A-J, May-July 1948 (Box 86, Folder 1065)
      - Correspondence, Delegates to WSCF Summer Conferences P-Z, April-July 1948 (Box 86, Folder 1066)
      - WSCF Bible Study Training Course, Les Marecottes, Switzerland, Circular Letters, Correspondence re. Delegates, and memos, April -June 1948 (Box 86, Folder 1067)
      - WSCF Chalet, Memos and travel brochure, April 1948 (Box 86, Folder 1068)
      - WSCF Conference on Missions, Zeist, Holland, Correspondence re. Delegates, memos, and notes from John Deschner, June-July 1948 (Box 86, Folder 1069)
      - WSCF Conference, The University and the Technical Age, Correspondence re. Delegates and provisional minutes, May-July 1948 (Box 86, Folder 1070)
      - WSCF Asian Leaders' Conference, Kandy, Ceylon, Conference handbook and memos, 1948-1949 (Box 86, Folder 1071)
      - WSCF Annual Conference, Memos and notes from John Deschner, July 1950 (Box 86, Folder 1072)
      - WSCF Summer Conferences, Correspondence re. Delegates, May 1950 (Box 87, Folder 1073)
      - WSCF Summer Conferences, Correspondence re. Delegates, May-June 1950 (Box 87, Folder 1074)
      - WSCF Theological Student Conference, Correspondence re. Delegates, memos, and study outlines, March-June 1948 (Box 87, Folder 1075)
      - WSCF Study Chalet, Correspondence re. Delegates and memos, 1951 (Box 87, Folder 1076)
      - WSCF Summer Conferences, Correspondence and memos, 1951 (Box 87, Folder 1077)
      - Third World Conference of Christian Youth, Travancore, India, American Committee, Correspondence re. Delegates, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 1078)
      - Third World Conference of Christian Youth, Travancore, India, American Committee, Correspondence, Marksman, Charles and Lulla, 1951-1952 (Box 87, Folder 1079)
      - Third World Conference of Christian Youth, Travancore, India, American Committee, Correspondence re. Publicity, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 1080)
      - Third World Conference of Christian Youth, Travancore, India, American Committee, Memos, meeting agendas, and minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 87, Folder 1081)
      - Third World Conference of Christian Youth, Travancore, India, USCC, Correspondence, Delegates, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 1082)
      - Third World Conference of Christian Youth, Travancore, India, USCC, Correspondence, Knutson, Kent, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 1083)
      - Third World Conference of Christian Youth, Travancore, India, USCC, Delegate nominations includes photographs, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 1084)
      - Third World Conference of Christian Youth, Travancore, India, USCC, Publicity including brochures, news releases, pamphlet, and World Communique Vol. LXII, No. 2 April 1952 (Box 87, Folder 1085)
      - WSCF Summer Conferences, Correspondence re. fraternal delegates, 1956 (Box 87, Folder 1086)
  - Other Conferences
    - National Assembly of the Student Christian Association Movement, University of Illinois, Conference materials, brochures, prospectus, December 27, 1946-January 3, 1947 (Box 88, Folder 1087)
    - Second Annual General Assembly of United World Federalists, Inc, Minneapolis, MN, Bye-laws, proposed agenda, report of the conference by Kent Knutson, and schedule of events, November 11-14, 1948 (Box 88, Folder 1088)
    - Illinois Ecumenical Conference, Correspondence re. leadership suggestions, 1950 (Box 88, Folder 1089)
    - Ecumenical Student Conference, Wayland Academy, Beaver Dam, WI, Brochures and correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 88, Folder 1090)
    - Third Annual Ecumenical Conference, Texas A&M College, Roster and summary report, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 1091)
    - New York State S.C.M. Summer Conference, Cooperstown, NY, Orientation packet, June 8-14, 1957 (Box 88, Folder 1092)
    - NCCC Consultation on "Moral Responsibility and Nuclear Space Problem," Government document: The Nature of Radioactive Fallout and Its Effects on Man, notes of Herluf Jensen, pamphlets including Atomic Test and Disarmament, The Churches and the United Nations, The New United Nations, and resolutions adopted by the NCCC General Assembly, December 13-15, 1957 (Box 88, Folder 1093)
    - Convention of Episcopal Young Churchmen, Oberlin College, Oberlin, OH, Directory, Information sheets, and study guide., August 20-27, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 1094)
    - National Consultative Conference on Religion and the State University, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI, Orientation packet, November 16-19, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 1095)
- USCC Publications and Printed Materials, Series V
  - Bibliographies, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 1096)
  - Book, Chosen Peoples by Denis Baly includes pamphlet Comments on Chosen People, 1956 (Box 88, Folder 1097)
  - Booklet, Colleges and Universities--Yesterday and Today (study guide), May 1957 (Box 88, Folder 1098)
  - Booklet, A Manual for Local Cooperative Student Christian Work issued by the Campus Strategy Committee of the United Student Christian Council and The S.C.M. and the World (Box 88, Folder 1099)
  - Brochures, USCC related includes drafts and proof, 1946-1958 (Box 88, Folder 1100)
  - Brochures, WSCF related, 1946-1958 (Box 88, Folder 1101)
  - Circular letters, Doc 3-1 to 3-31, 1946 (Box 89, Folder 1102)
  - Circular letters, Doc 3-1 to 3-77 (drafts), 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 1103)
  - Circular letters, Doc 3-32 to 3-58, 1947 (Box 89, Folder 1104)
  - Circular letters, Doc 3-59 to 3-78, 1947 (Box 89, Folder 1105)
  - Circular letters, Doc 3-78 to 3-120 (drafts), 1947 (Box 89, Folder 1106)
  - Circular letters, Doc 3-79 to 3-123, 1947 (Box 89, Folder 1107)
  - Circular letters, Doc 4-23 to 4-61, 1947 (Box 89, Folder 1108)
  - Circular letters, Doc 4-62 to 4-94, 1947-1948 (Box 90, Folder 1109)
  - Circular letters, Doc 4-94 to 4-110, 1948 (Box 90, Folder 1110)
  - Circular letters, Doc 4-111 to 4-132, 1948 (Box 90, Folder 1111)
  - Circular letters, Doc 5-1 to 5-32, 1948-1949 (Box 90, Folder 1112)
  - Circular letters, Doc 5-33 to 5-60, 1949 (Box 90, Folder 1113)
  - Circular letters, Doc 6-1 to 6-23, 1949-1950 (Box 90, Folder 1114)
  - Circular letters, Doc 6-25 to 6-63, 6-83, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 1115)
  - Circular letters, Doc 7-1 to 7-25, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 1116)
  - Circular letters, Doc 7-26 to 7-37, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 1117)
  - Circular letters, Doc 7-37 to 7-57, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 1118)
  - Circular letters, Doc 7-55 to 7-78, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 1119)
  - Circular letters, Doc 8-1 to 8-24, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 1120)
  - Circular letters, Doc 8-27 to 8-70, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 1121)
  - Circular letters, Doc 9-10 to 9-100 (incomplete run), 1952-1953 (Box 92, Folder 1122)
  - Circular letters, Doc 12-6 to 12-33 (incomplete run), 1955-1956 (Box 92, Folder 1123)
  - Circular letters, Doc 12-37 to 12-95 (incomplete run), 1956 (Box 92, Folder 1124)
  - Circular letters, Doc 13-1 to 13-81, 1956-1957 (Box 92, Folder 1125)
  - Circular letters, Doc 13-82 to 13-122, 1957 (Box 92, Folder 1126)
  - Circular letters, Doc 13-123 to 13-166, 1957 (Box 92, Folder 1127)
  - Circular letters, Doc 13-167 to 13-205, 1957 (Box 92, Folder 1128)
  - Circular letters, Doc 13-218 to 13-247, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 1129)
  - Circular letters, Doc 13-250 to 13-311, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 1130)
  - Circular letters, Doc 14-1 to 14-50, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 1131)
  - Circular letters, Doc 14-50 to 14-113, 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 1132)
  - Circular letters, Doc 14-116 to 14-166, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 1133)
  - Circular letters, Doc 14-167 to 14-234, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 1134)
  - Circular letters, Doc 15-1 to 15-67, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 1135)
  - Circular letters, Doc 15-68 to 15-127, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 1136)
  - Circular letters, Doc 15-129 to 15-218, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 1137)
  - Document mailings, 1946 (Box 94, Folder 1138)
  - Flyer, Attention! American Students, 1946 (Box 94, Folder 1139)
  - Memos, 1944-1950, 1952 (Box 94, Folder 1140)
  - Memos, 1954-1957 (Box 94, Folder 1141)
  - Newsletter, Bulletin re. The Life and Mission of the Church project includes proof, July 1958 (Box 94, Folder 1142)
  - Newsletter, Communique, 1942-1944 (Box 94, Folder 1143)
  - Newsletter, Communique, 1946-1947 (Box 94, Folder 1144)
  - Newsletter, Communique, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 1145)
  - Newsletter, Communique, 1950 (Box 95, Folder 1146)
  - Newsletter, Communique, 1951 (Box 95, Folder 1147)
  - Newsletter, Communique, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 1148)
  - Newsletter, Communique, 1953 (Box 95, Folder 1149)
  - Newsletter, Communique, January-June 1954 (Box 95, Folder 1150)
  - Newsletter, Communique, July-December 1954 (Box 95, Folder 1151)
  - Newsletter, Communique, 1955 (Box 95, Folder 1152)
  - Newsletter, Communique, 1956-1957 (Box 96, Folder 1153)
  - Newsletter, Communique, 1958-1959 (Box 96, Folder 1154)
  - Newsletter, Federation News Sheet, 1937-1940 (Box 96, Folder 1155)
  - Newsletter, Federation News Sheet, 1941-1945 (Box 96, Folder 1156)
  - Newsletter, Federation News Sheet, 1946-1947 (Box 96, Folder 1157)
  - Newsletter, Federation News Sheet, 1948-1950 (Box 96, Folder 1158)
  - News Releases includes biographical information, 1949, 1951-1954 (Box 96, Folder 1159)
  - Pamphlet, Introducing WSCF, 1947 (Box 96, Folder 1160)
  - Pamphlets, The Christian Student and the Church and The Christian Student and the World Struggle by J. Robert Nelson, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 1160)
  - Pamphlet, The Why and How of Group Study by Nansie Blackie includes proof, 1952 (Box 97, Folder 1161)
  - Pamphlet, The Church and the World: Four Bible Studies Based on the Gospel of John by Bernhard W. Anderson, Citizens of God's Kingdom: a Study Guide to the Sermon on the Mount, and USCC Practical Guide no. 2-4, 1954, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 1162)
  - Pamphlet, Ecumenical Conversations for Students and In Quest of Encounter: a Triologue on s.C.m. Responsibility for those from Abroad by Ruth Haines Purkaple, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 1163)
  - Pamphlet, Christ in You: a Study Guide for Paul's Letter to the Collosians, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 1164)
  - Pamphlets, The Bible, the Church, and the Student Christian Movement by Harvey Cox and Witness to the Truth, circa 1958 (Box 97, Folder 1165)
  - Pamphlets, The Evangelization of the University and the WSCF Handbook (Box 97, Folder 1166)
  - Papers, Green Lake papers and A Protestant SCM? by Ray Sweetman, 1948-1949, 1954 (Box 97, Folder 1167)
  - Report, Third Annual Meeting of the United Student Christian Council, October 22-26, 1946 (Box 97, Folder 1168)
  - Report, Fourth Annual Meeting of the United Student Christian Council, September 6-12, 1947 (Box 97, Folder 1169)
  - Report, Fifth Annual Meeting of the United Student Christian Council, September 11-16, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 1170)
  - Report, Sixth General Assembly of the United Student Christian Council and Seventh General Assembly of the United Student Christian Council, August 31-September 4, 1949, September 2-10, 1950 (Box 97, Folder 1171)
  - Report, Eighth General Assembly of the United Student Christian Council, September 1-8, 1951 (Box 97, Folder 1172)
  - Report, Ninth General Assembly of the United Student Christian Council, September 6-13, 1952 (Box 97, Folder 1173)
  - Report, Tenth General Assembly of the United Student Christian Council, September 5-12, 1953 (Box 98, Folder 1174)
  - Report, Eleventh General Assembly of the United Student Christian Council, September 5-10, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 1175)
  - Report, Twelfth General Assembly of the United Student Christian Council, September 3-10, 1955 (Box 98, Folder 1176)
  - Report, Thirteenth General Assembly of the United Student Christian Council, September 5 -11, 1956 (Box 98, Folder 1177)
  - Report, Fourteenth General Assembly of the United Student Christian Council, September 5-11, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 1178)
- USCC Organization and Policy Records, Series VI
  - Annual files, 1946 (Box 99, Folder 1179)
  - Annual files, 1946-1947 (Box 99, Folder 1180)
  - Annual files, 1947 (Box 99, Folder 1181)
  - Annual files, 1947 (Box 99, Folder 1182)
  - Annual files, 1947 (Box 99, Folder 1183)
  - Annual files, 1947-1948 (Box 99, Folder 1184)
  - Annual files, 1948-1949 (Box 100, Folder 1185)
  - Annual files, 1949-1950 (Box 100, Folder 1186)
  - Annual files, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1187)
  - Annual files, 1951-1952 (Box 100, Folder 1188)
  - Appointments to USCC committees, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 1189)
  - Appointments to USCC committees, 1955-1956 (Box 101, Folder 1190)
  - Appointments to USCC committees, 1956-1957 (Box 101, Folder 1191)
  - Appointments to USCC committees, 1957-1958 (Box 101, Folder 1192)
  - Biography sketches of USCC member movements, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 1193)
  - Chart of involvements including glossary of symbols, 1957 (Box 101, Folder 1194)
  - Directory of USCC, 1944-1951, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 1195)
  - Employee time sheets, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 1196)
  - Formation of USCC documents, September 15, 1944 (Box 101, Folder 1197)
  - Form letters, 1957 (Box 101, Folder 1198)
  - Mailing lists, 1944-1951 (Box 101, Folder 1199)
  - Mailing lists, 1954-1955 (Box 101, Folder 1200)
  - Mailing lists, 195? (Box 101, Folder 1201)
  - Mailing lists of member movements, 1946-1952 (Box 101, Folder 1202)
  - Materials for Herluf Jensen's speeches, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1203)
  - Meeting Schedules, 1951, 1958-1959 (Box 102, Folder 1204)
  - Member movement constitutions, 1945 (Box 102, Folder 1205)
  - Memos, miscellaneous, 1958-1959 (Box 102, Folder 1206)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1207)
  - Notes from Herluf Jensen, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1208)
  - Office location of the USCC includes maps of office layout, 1956 (Box 102, Folder 1209)
  - Office procedures, 1944-1945 (Box 102, Folder 1210)
  - Office procedures, 1955-1956 (Box 102, Folder 1211)
  - Office supplies and orders, 1948-1952 (Box 102, Folder 1212)
  - Photo negatives of USCC staff, Spring 1957 (Box 102, Folder 1213)
  - Student chairmen of member movements, 1953 (Box 102, Folder 1214)
  - Student Volunteer Movement--USCC inter office relations, 1948 (Box 102, Folder 1215)
  - Tax information, 1946 (Box 102, Folder 1216)
  - USCC articles of operation, constitution, and by-laws, 1944-1954 (Box 102, Folder 1217)
  - Working file of Associate Executive Secretaries Gretli Wieser and Mimi Gowen, 1950-1952 (Box 102, Folder 1218)
  - Working file of Executive Secretary Herluf Jensen, 1950-1952 (Box 103, Folder 1219)
  - Working file of Executive Secretary Herluf Jensen, 1950-1952 (Box 103, Folder 1220)
  - Working file of student chairman, Kent Knutson re. executive committee, 1948-1952 (Box 103, Folder 1221)
  - Working file of student chairman Kent Knutson re. general, 1948-1952 (Box 103, Folder 1222)
  - Working file of student chairman Kent Knutson re. USCC statement of purpose, 1951-1952 (Box 103, Folder 1223)
  - Working file for WSCF secretary Hazel Hill, 1947-1949 (Box 103, Folder 1224)
  - Worship documents, 1945-1950 (Box 103, Folder 1225)
- World Student Christian Federation, Series VII
  - WSCF Commissions
    - Ecumenical and University Commission
      - Ecumenical Commission, Correspondence, circular letters and reports, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 1226)